

lucydsouza1996@gmail.com | +91 95909 73065 | Ahmedabad, GJ 380015

Summary

Detail-oriented Accountant with 3 years of effectively maintaining accurate accounting information for financial organizations. History of working as part of financial team to manage diverse financial functions and reporting.

Skills

- P>Tally ERP
- P>Accounting

- P>Bookkeeping
- P>Finance

Experience

Cygnet Infotech Pvt Ltd | Ahmedabad Accounts Executive

01/2022 - Current

- Managing entire invoicing cycle from getting PO to proving invoice to client.
- Preparing monthly sales and collection report with product wise detail.
- Preparing monthly outstanding report with sales POC detail.
- Solving problem for clients with invoice and ledger reconciliation.

St. Joseph's Educational Medical Relief | Hubli, Karnataka Accountant Specialist

09/2019 - 09/2020

- Preparing payroll and employee claims to resolve discrepancies and balance financial records.
- Managed payroll for organization.
- Compared identifying information in computers with Tally.
- Applied knowledge of regulations, employment law and EPF to keep operations in compliance with applicable standards.

SDM College of Medical Sciences | Dharwad, Karnataka **Office Assistant** 01/2018 - 01/2019

- Worked in health package department.
- Delivered clerical support by handling range of routine and special requirements.
- Produced high-quality documents, spreadsheets and presentations for internal and customer-facing needs.
- Completed clerical tasks such as filing, copying and distributing mail.
- Verified accuracy of business records by consistently updating customer information.
- Drafted common document templates for use by executives and employees.

Education and Training

IGNOU | Dharwad, Karnataka Master of Commerce in Accounting And Finance

CSI College of Commerce | Dharwad, Karnataka **Bachelor of Commerce** in Accounting

Languages —
 English Hindi Kannada
Certifications
Tally ERP 9
Interests
Cooking
References —
• Will be provided later ************************************